

### Personal info

Born in Terrassa (Barcelona) on 03.02.1994

bernatferrerm@gmail.com

+34 601436012 +49 5770251085

♣ Pl. Josep Freixa i Argemí 08221 Terrassa (Spain)

### Languages

 Catalan:
 • • • • •

 Spanish:
 • • • • •

 English:
 • • • • •

 German:
 • • • • •

### **Programming Languages**

Python:

Kotlin:

C++:

Javascript:

HTML / CSS:

SQL:

R:

● ● ● ● ●

● ○ ○

■ ○ ○ ○

■ ○ ○ ○

■ ○ ○ ○ ○

## Software tools

Git:
Linux:
Latex:
Android:
Godot:
Unity:
Excel:

Contact of the c

### Interests

- Software development
- Science
- Language learning

### **Hobbies**

- Develop games/apps
- Chess
- Boulder climbing
- Hiking
- Jogging
- Scientific reading

# **Bernat Ferrer**

### **Developer and Physicist**

### About me

I am a 26 year old software developer and Physicist, currently enrolled in a master in software development, specialized in full stack. I am opened to new experiences or projects, as well as curious about several areas of the knowledge.

### **Education**

Full-Stack Master Assembler School of Software Engineering, Barcelona. 2020-Now

Astrophysics Master Ludwig Maximilians University, Munich (LMU). 2017-2019

Physics Degree Universitat Autónoma de Barcelona (UAB). 2012-2017

Primary and Highschool Escola Pia, Terrassa. 1997-2012.

### Additionally

An app for language learning, published in google play and developed using AndroidStudio.

- App Link ⇒ play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.berni.android.prototype1lanbase
- Repository⇒ github.com/berni23/Language-database
- Design⇒ figma.com/file/P0yRZO7FUfdGh5rrbOMTyC/LanguageDatabase?node-id=47 %3A19

A user experience course (UX) in LMU, Munich. Winter Semester 2019/20.

Development of a small game using the Godot platform. 2019

A six month internship in the European southern observatory (ESO) in Munich. April -September 2018.

Volunteer in a homeless shelter in the city of Pittsburgh, USA. Summer 2013.

### **Professional experience**

Data analyst Data Analyst in M-net for one year. September 2018 - October 2019.

**Private math teacher** Private math lessons for students for four years in Terrassa, Spain. 2012-2016.

**Monitor in a summer camp** Monitor in an English summer camp for children in Spain, with *Món Idiomes academy*. Summer 2016.

Administrator in a Winery Administrative tasks in the winery *Celler de l'Era*, Spain. Summers 2010-2015.

# Sites

GitHub github.com/berni23

Linkedin linkedin.com/in/bernat-ferrer-bb3446159

Stack Overflow stackoverflow.com/users/7569812/brny

Wordpress textos983595804.wordpress.com

Twitter twitter.com/hashtac